COLT MCANLIS: 嘿  大家好
COLT MCANLIS: Hey everybody.
我是Colt McAnlis
My name is Colt McAnlis.
我在这儿来看一下身后Google数据中心
And I'm here to take a quick look behind the scenes
的一些场景
at some of Google's data centers.
你知道的  在3月25日  Google云平台
You see, on March 25, the Google Cloud Platform
到时候会有一个激动人心的计划
has an exciting event planned that you're not
你一定不想错过它
going to want to miss.
但是在那之前  我觉得
But before then, I figured it would
最好来看一下Google引擎是如何工作的
be good to take a look at how Google works under the hood.
因为当你谈及Google的时候
Because when you talk about Google,
你一定会谈到是它的规模
what you're really talking about is scale.
你要知道  我们每个月会提供超过60亿小时的YouTube视频
You see, we serve over 6 billion hours of YouTube video
的服务
every single month.
同时  还有来自Google的1000亿次的搜索服务
And at the same time, service 100 billion searches from Google.
我个人所喜欢的  是每分钟激活1000台
And my personal favorite, activate 1,000 Android devices
Android设备
every single minute.
在如此大规模的地方工作不是件容易的任务
Working at that scale is no easy task.
我们需要构建一个全球范围的基础设施来处理这样的负载
We've had to build a global infrastructure to handle the load.
一切都是从横跨太平洋铺设光纤
Everything from laying fiber across the Pacific Ocean
建设数据中心开始的
to building data centers that blur
它模糊了科学  艺术  和创造一些伟大的事情的工具之间的界限
the line between science, art, and utility to create something great.
例如  我们来看一下这个坐落在俄勒冈州的数据中心
For example, take a look at this data center in Oregon.
所有这些的彩色管道不是为了作秀
All of these colored pipes here are not just for show.
每种颜色都代表了详细的
Each color details important information
关于水温和流向的重要信息  相信我
about the water temperature and flow direction, which trust me,
当你想要尝试跟踪管道泄露时
is important when you're trying to track down
这是很重要的
a leak in miles of tubing.
看一下这排位于佐治亚州的服务器
And take a look at this row of servers in Georgia.
这些大功率的节能LED
These energy-efficient high-powered LEDs
让我们知道服务器机架上的一切都运行的很平稳
let us know that everything is running smoothly in the server rack.
这个数据中心在南卡罗来纳州
And this data center in South Carolina
承载了一个三层楼机器的仓库
hosts a three-story warehouse of machines.
当这其中的一个出现故障
When one of these bad boys break down,
这里的自动机器人  实际上会抓取到磁盘驱动器
that automated robot over there, actually grabs the tape drive
并移除掉
and removes it for you.
最棒的部分就是所有的这些技术
The best part about all this technology
都是我们不只是为我们自己所用
is that we're not keeping it to ourselves.
通过Google云平台的力量
Through the power of the Google Cloud Platform,
你可以访问同样运行Google基础设施的
you've got access to the same network, compute,
网络  计算和存储服务
and storage that runs all of Google's infrastructure.
并且它提供了一个方式允许你配置  匹配
And it's offered in a way that allows you to mix, match,
和组合的应用程序接口和服务  来满足你的应用程序的需求
and combine APIs and services to fit your application needs.
这确实是Snapchat开发者所做的
Which is exactly what the Snapchat developers did.
你要知道  他们的四人小团队
You see, they're small four-person team was
就能够影响Google App Engine的可扩展能力
able to leverage the scalable power of Google App Engine
使Snapchat成为2013年最热门的下载应用
to make Snapchat one of the hottest downloads of 2013,
每天服务超过35千万张照片
serving over 350 million photos a day.
再来考虑一下Song Pop的人们  他们在很短的几个月内
And consider the Song Pop folks, who in a few short months,
从默默无闻到每天服务2500万的活跃用户
went from obscurity to serving 2.5 million daily active users,
而仅仅是雇佣了一个工程师
while only assigning a single engineer to worry
来担心性能和运行时间的问题
about performance and uptime.
这确实是你期待的
Which is exactly what you'd expect
当你运行在同样的准确的硬件和软件
when you're running on the same exact hardware and software
来自Google服务的力量
that powers all of Google services.
当我们谈论到Cloud提供的功能时
When we're talking about Cloud offerings,
很容易陷入细节关键词
it's really easy to get bogged down in the minutia
比如站点隔离  或者虚拟机
of key words like site isolation, or virtual machines,
或者负载均衡
or load balancing.
有时我们忘了很小的事情  螺母
And sometimes we forget the small stuff, the nuts,
螺栓  焊锡线  接头  散热器
the bolts, the solder wires, the joints, the cooling fans,
供水系统  当然  甚至这些带颜色的管道
the water towers, and yes, even the colored pipes
使其完全的工作起来
that make it all work.
你知道  我们在Google的15年中已经建立了
You see, for 15 years we at Google have been building
美丽的强大的数据中心
beautiful powerful data centers.
所有的这些力量是你现在的命令
And all that power is now at your command.
请确保你在Google+上加入了Google云平台的社区
Make sure you join the Google Cloud Platform community on Google+.
并且不要忘了在3月25日回到这里
And don't forget to come back here on March 25 for an event
为一场你不想做过的大事
that you're not going to want to miss.
我是Colt McAnlis
My name is Colt McAnlis.
现在开始  去创造一些伟大的事情吧
Now, go build something great.